
   { 
    "responseStatus": "SUCCESS",
    "results" :[
    {
      "question":"What song was performed by Ramones?",
      "wrongAnswers": [ "Allergic to you", "Never ever", "Judy is a punk"],
      "answer":"Pet sematary"
    },
    {
      "question":"Who is the vocalist of Aerosmith?",
      "wrongAnswers":["James Hetfield", "Brian Johnson", "Robert Plant"],
      "answer": "Steven Tyler"
    },
    {
      "question": "Click the correct answer",
      "wrongAnswers":["Richie Sambora is a member of The Clash", "The Beatles splited in 1980","Alice Cooper was created in 1969"],
      "answer": "Ozzy Osboune is the vocalist of Black Sabbath"
    },
    {
       "question":  "Which band is the oldest?" ,
       "wrongAnswers": ["Aerosmith" , "AC/DC", "Guns n' Roses"],
       "answer" : "Queen"
    },
    
    {
       "question": "Where is the Band Genesis From?",
       "wrongAnswers": ["Sweden", "Norway", "EEUU"],
       "answer":"England"
    },
    {
       "question":"What song is from Alice Cooper?",
       "wrongAnswers":["Home sweet home", "Stairway to heaven", "Highway to hell"],
       "answer":"Hey stoopid"
    },
    {
       "question":"What album is from Pink Floyd?",
       "wrongAnswers":["Abbey road", "Paranoid", "Who is next"],
       "answer":"The wall"
    },
    {
      "question":"Who is the leader of The Cure?",
      "wrongAnswers":["Brian Johnson", "Glenn Frey", "Joe Elliott"],
      "answer":"Robert Smith"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is a member of Montley Cr√ºe?",
      "wrongAnswers":["Robert Smith","Ray Wilson", "Joke Berg"],
      "answer":"Nicky Sixx"
    },
    {
     "question":"What band has been live for the longest period of time?",
     "wrongAnswers": ["AC/DC", "The Who", "KISS"],
     "answer":"The Rolling Stones"
    }
    ]
   }